

Reshma Jadhav

Wismar | Germany | Information Technology and Services

Software Test Engineer | Quality Analyst

Contact: +4915906779344

Email: jagtapdakshayani23@gmail.com

Key Skills

Describes main experiences and knowledge.

Requirements analysis and management, Manual Testing, API Testing, Object Oriented Programming, Agile-SCRUM, Automation Testing, Quality Assurance and Quality Control, Team collaboration, Client Communication, Team leading, Knowledge sharing, Telecommunication and Healthcare domain knowledge

Selected projects Shows list of all your significant projects.

Infosys - GSK (09/2021-12/2021)

Worked as an individual tester and was involved in all QA activities. Within a short time span, I was able to meet the changing user requirements. Got appreciated from clients for delivering quality software together with agile team members

Responsibilities:

- Standardized Test plan, Test scripts, Execution, Investigating and fixing bugs, Scrum Reporting.
- Test demo creation and presentation to the clients.

Infosys- Pfizer (05/2020 - 08/2021)

As a senior member of testing team I played important role to release a quality software to end user in multiple healthcare domain applications. Managing and analyzing business and user requirements. Worked in multiple agile teams.

Responsibilities:

- Collaboration with development team
- **Exploratory Testing**
- **Functional and Database testing**
- Worked as a test lead for a project and presented to the client.
- Established proper team communication that identified, triaged, reproduced and fixed found issues.
- Received INSTA award for my contribution in successfully handling a critical application
- Tools and technologies used: JIRA, Zephyr, MYSQL

Infosys – British Telecom (12/2019 – 04/2020)

As a Flow Designer I was involved monitoring and supporting development and deployment activities. Responsibilities:

- **Development support**
- Involved in deployment and Production support
- Tools and technologies used: BT's internal tools ESCAMP (Flow Design), Eclipse, GIT, ORACLE-SQL

Accenture – British Telecom (04/2015 – 11/2019)

Joined as a junior tester and got promoted to senior level. Involved in most of the SDLC and STLC activities. Had daily basis calls/meetings with BA and stakeholders for requirement analysis. Responsibilities:

- System testing, Integration testing, Regression.
- Traceability Matrix to fill in the gap between requirements and test covered contributing to the 10% increase in the test case count
- **Production support**
- Presentation to the PO/BA/Client
- Tools and technologies used :HP ALM, Excel, Siebel CRM
- Received Apex award and BT recognition award for delivering new product successfully.

Experience

Shows list of previous employers and positions.

Senior Software Tester

Infosys

December 2019 - December 2021, India

- Requirement Analysis and Test planning
- E2E Testing
- Root Cause Analysis
- Code Review
- Deployment
- Production Support post release to monitor defects raised.
- Leadership

Senior Software Tester

Accenture

April 2017- November 2019, India

- Requirement Analysis
- Traceability Matrix
- Test planning, Test Design
- Scrum meetings
- Test Execution Reports
- Mentoring and Knowledge sharing

Junior Software Tester

Accenture

April 2015 - March 2017, India

- Test execution
- Bug investigation and reporting
- Cross product Testing
- Black Box test design techniques
- Test Execution-Functional, Regression, Sanity, GUI testing.

Education

Highest level of education.

- June 2013 April 2015 MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATION Savitribai Phule University, Pune, India Information Technology Studies
- June 2010 April 2013 BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE Shivaji University, Kolhapur, India



English: B2 (detail description of CEFR levels)
German: A2 (detail description of CEFR levels)

Trainings & Certificates

Selenium with core JAVA, Udemy.com
Restful API using POSTMAN Testing Course
German A1 Certificate, Goethe India
HP ALM and JIRA Training

Tools and techniques

Cucumber-BDD(Gherkin), Page Object Model,TestNG,Gl Apache Maven ORACLE-SQL,MS Office, MS Excel, IDE Eclipse, MS PowerPoint, , Jenkins, Siebel CRM, TDD, ATD